Contact

erhardt.jeffrey@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/jeff-erhardt-76a9627 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Underwriting Real Estate Debt

Jeff Erhardt

Managing Director and Chief Investment Officer at White Oak Healthcare REIT, I, LLC

Washington D.C. Metro Area

Summary

Commercial real estate investment professional with over 25 years of experience in deal sourcing, underwriting, asset management and work out of debt and equity investments. Experience includes all types of commercial real estate assets. The past 17 years have been focused on equity investments in healthcare real estate including seniors housing and skilled nursing.

Experience

White Oak Healthcare REIT, I, LLC
Managing Director and Chief Investment Officer
March 2019 - Present (1 year 5 months)

Washington D.C. Metro Area

- Co-Founder of White Oak Healthcare REIT I, LLC, a healthcare real estate investment vehicle focused primarily on equity investments in senior housing and skilled nursing properties in the US.
- Head of all aspects of the healthcare real estate investment platform including deal sourcing, underwriting, asset management and investor reporting.
- Focused investments include NNN lease and JV equity structures for skilled nursing, assisted living, memory care, independent living and CCRC facilities.

Capital Healthcare Investments, LLC
Co-Founder and Managing Director
August 2015 - February 2019 (3 years 7 months)

Washington D.C. Metro Area

- Founder of Capital Healthcare Investments, LLC in August 2015, a healthcare real estate investment fund focused primarily on equity investments in senior housing and skilled nursing properties in the US.

- Head of all aspects of the healthcare real estate investment platform including deal sourcing, underwriting, asset management and investor reporting.
- Focused investments include NNN lease and JV equity structures as well as mezzanine debt for skilled nursing, assisted living, memory care, independent living and CCRC facilities.
- Acquired over \$300MM in assets across 25 properties, aligned with 5 high quality operators with a mix of skilled nursing and senior housing assets under both NNN lease and JV structures.

GE Capital

Managing Director; Healthcare Real Estate Equity September 2003 - August 2015 (12 years) Bethesda, MD

AMI Capital

Deputy Chief Underwriter September 1998 - September 2003 (5 years 1 month)

AMRESCO

Senior Investment Officer September 1997 - September 1998 (1 year 1 month)

Allied Capital AVP 1994 - 1997 (3 years)

Education

Marymount University MBA

Salisbury University - Perdue School of Business Finance

University of Baltimore Merrick School of Business